<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NotaLs</string>
    <string name="intro">
     From the home screen, we have three cards menus each giving information about each of the three use cases of this application. To navigate to
        any of the three uses you can press on the arrow provided on each card.
    </string>
    <string name="preparation">
        For preparations you can add one by pressing on float button filling the required fields on the preparation form and
        then pressing on add. To edit you just long press on the respective item card and edit on the fields.\n For activities, on pressing on the activities icon button,
        you navigate to activities. To add an item, you press on the floating button to get a popup where you can provide the required data and add an activity.
        \n To update you can just long press on the respective card activity to change what you desire to change by editing.

    </string>
    <string name="shopping">
        For shopping you can add one by pressing on float button filling the required fields on the shopping form screen and
        then pressing on add. To edit you just press on the update button of the respective item card the form provided is pre-populated.
        On it you can edit the fields as you desire.\n
         For shopping items, on pressing on the cart icon button,
        you navigate to shopping items where you can add an item by pressing on the floating button to get a popup where you provide the required data and add an item. \n To update you can just long press on the respective card item to change
        what you desire to change by editing on the fields.
    </string>
    <string name="services">
         For services you can add one by pressing on float button filling the required fields on the add service form screen and
        then pressing on add. To edit you just long press on the respective item card the form provided as result is pre-populated with data.
        On it you can edit the fields as you desire.\n
    </string>
</resources>